-DOCSTART- -X- O O

When WRB _ O
Sebastian NNP _ B-PERSON
Thrun NNP _ I-PERSON
started VBD _ O
working VBG _ O
on IN _ O
self NN _ O
- HYPH _ O
driving VBG _ O
cars NNS _ O
at IN _ O
Google NNP _ B-ORG
in IN _ O
2007 CD _ B-DATE
, , _ O
few JJ _ O
people NNS _ O
outside RB _ O
of IN _ O
the DT _ O
company NN _ O
took VBD _ O
him PRP _ O
seriously RB _ O
. . _ O

“ '' _ O
I PRP _ O
can MD _ O
tell VB _ O
you PRP _ O
very RB _ O
senior JJ _ O
CEOs NNS _ O
of IN _ O
major JJ _ O
American JJ _ B-NORP
car NN _ O
companies NNS _ O
would MD _ O
shake VB _ O
my PRP$ _ O
hand NN _ O
and CC _ O
turn VB _ O
away RB _ O
because IN _ O
I PRP _ O
was VBD _ O
n’t RB _ O
worth JJ _ O
talking VBG _ O
to IN _ O
, , _ O
” '' _ O
said VBD _ O
Thrun NNP _ B-PERSON
, , _ O
in IN _ O
an DT _ O
interview NN _ O
with IN _ O
Recode NNP _ B-ORG
earlier RBR _ B-DATE
this DT _ I-DATE
week NN _ I-DATE
. . _ O

